<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on</title><link>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/overview/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/overview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/overview/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/overview/introduction/</guid><description>WAHA - WhatsApp HTTP API that you can install on your own server and run in less than 5 minutes!
Get started #
👉 Run WhatsApp HTTP API in less than 5 minutes! We will guide you through the necessary steps to successfully send your first text message using WhatsApp HTTP API in Quick Start →.
Features #
WAHA is distributed in two versions:
Core - the basic version that meet almost 80% people&amp;rsquo;s needs.</description></item><item><title>Quick Start</title><link>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/overview/quick-start/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/overview/quick-start/</guid><description>On this page you&amp;rsquo;re going to install WAHA, run it, authenticate the client using QR code and send the first text message to WhatsApp!
Requirements #
Only thing that you must have - installed docker. Please follow the original instruction how to install docker -&amp;gt;.
When you are ready - come back and follows the below steps to send the first text message to WhatsApp via HTTP API!
Why Docker?
Docker makes it easy to ship all-in-one solution with the runtime and dependencies.</description></item><item><title>How to Avoid Blocking</title><link>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/overview/how-to-avoid-blocking/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 13:26:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/overview/how-to-avoid-blocking/</guid><description>How to Avoid Blocking in WhatsApp when developing bots.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to keep in mind that WhatsApp has strict policies in place to prevent spamming and abuse of their platform.
If you&amp;rsquo;re developing a bot for WhatsApp, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to follow these guidelines to avoid getting blocked.
Guidelines to Follow #
1. Only Reply to Messages #
When developing a bot for WhatsApp, you should never initiate a conversation. Instead, your bot should only reply to messages that it receives.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/overview/faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/overview/faq/</guid><description>How much CPU and Memory does WhatsApp HTTP API consume? #
The benchmark has been made on Intel(R) Core(TM) i7-10510U CPU @ 1.80GHz. It may differ from case to case, it depends on usage pattern - how many messages you get, how many send, etc.
Accounts (sessions) in the container CPU Memory 1 30% 400MB 10 270% 1.5GB The nature of WhatsApp HTTP API and its underlying engines - is to run real WhatsApp Web version in Chrome and communicate with it to prevent blocking from WhatsApp.</description></item><item><title>Changelog</title><link>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/overview/changelog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/overview/changelog/</guid><description>If you wish to get and read Release Notes - read them on one of our platforms, these posts are FREE.
Boosty -&amp;gt; Patreon -&amp;gt; You even can subscribe to get new updates there!
2023.12 #
December 2023
Add chatId field to GET /api/contacts/check-exists to help get the right chatId for Brazilian numbers. Read more about error sending text to half of Brazilian numbers (every number registered before 2012) -&amp;gt; 2023.</description></item></channel></rss>