<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>How-to guides on</title><link>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/how-to/</link><description>Recent content in How-to guides on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/how-to/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Send messages</title><link>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/how-to/send-messages/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/how-to/send-messages/</guid><description>On your swagger documentation http://localhost:3000/ or in the example swagger you can find:
List of all supported methods - we have not documented all of them on the page Requests JSON schemas Responses JSON schemas Try it button - no additional setup to play around with a method Fields #
There are common fields that you can find in almost all requests:
session - a session name from which account you&amp;rsquo;re sending the message.</description></item><item><title>Receive messages</title><link>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/how-to/receive-messages/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/how-to/receive-messages/</guid><description>The project uses Webhooks to send the messages or events from WhatsApp to your application.
Webhooks #
You can configure where you want to receive events in environment variables:
WHATSAPP_HOOK_URL=https://httpbin.org/post - to set up a URL for the webhook WHATSAPP_HOOK_EVENTS=message,message.any,state.change,group.join,group.leave - specify events. DO NOT specify all of them, it&amp;rsquo;s too heavy payload, choose the right for you. WHATSAPP_HOOK_EVENTS=* - subscribe to all events. It&amp;rsquo;s not recommended for production, but it&amp;rsquo;s fine for development.</description></item><item><title>Configuration</title><link>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/how-to/config/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/how-to/config/</guid><description>You can configure WhatsApp HTTP API behaviour via environment variables, by adding -e WHATSAPP_VARNAME=value at the begging of the command line or by using other options
docker run -it -e WHATSAPP_HOOK_EVENTS=* -e WHATSAPP_HOOK_URL=https://httpbin.org/post devlikeapro/whatsapp-http-api Environment variables #
Common #
DEBUG=1 - show debug and verbose logs, set in any value WHATSAPP_API_PORT=3000 - listen port for HTTP server (default: 3000) WHATSAPP_API_HOSTNAME=localhost - Hostname for HTTP server (default: localhost) WHATSAPP_API_KEY=mysecret - protect the api with a secret code.</description></item><item><title>Engines</title><link>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/how-to/engines/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/how-to/engines/</guid><description>Under the hood WAHA allows you to use two different engines. You can control what you want to run by settings WHATSAPP_DEFAULT_ENGINE environment variables.
If you have any problems with one engine - try another!
👉 API responses and webhook payloads may differ significantly! We do our best to keep requests body stable between engines. WhatsApp WebJS #
WAHA uses WhatsApp WebJS engine by default
https://github.com/pedroslopez/whatsapp-web.js WHATSAPP_DEFAULT_ENGINE=WEBJS Venom #
https://github.com/orkestral/venom WHATSAPP_DEFAULT_ENGINE=VENOM</description></item><item><title>Security</title><link>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/how-to/security/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/how-to/security/</guid><description>💡 Do not expose WhatsApp HTTP API on public networks! We do not recommend exposing the API on any public networks!
Either protect the API with Api Key or deny access by using firewalls.
API security #
You can protect the API by requiring Api Key in a request&amp;rsquo;s headers.
Set Api Key #
Set WHATSAPP_API_KEY=yoursecretkey environment variable for that:
docker run -it -e WHATSAPP_API_KEY=yoursecretkey devlikeapro/whatsapp-http-api Swagger #
After you set api key - to authorize on swagger use Authorize button at the top: Add X-Api-Key header #
To authorize requests - set X-Api-Key header to yoursecretkey for all requests that go to WAHA.</description></item><item><title>Sessions</title><link>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/how-to/sessions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/how-to/sessions/</guid><description>Saving session #
Plus version allows you to save &amp;ldquo;session&amp;rdquo; state and avoid scanning QR code everytime when you start a container.
File storage #
If you want to save your session and do not scan QR code everytime when you launch WAHA - connect a local file storage to the container. WAHA stores authentication information in the directory and reuses it after restart.
Attach volume part to the command:</description></item><item><title>Plus version</title><link>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/how-to/plus-version/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/how-to/plus-version/</guid><description>Overview #
WAHA is distributed in two versions:
Core the basic version that meet almost 80% people’s needs. 100% free and open source. Plus the version with advanced messages, security, and reliability features. If you enjoy Core version and would like to support the project - you can subscribe on Core level. It&amp;rsquo;s not expensive, but it supports the project a lot!
Boosty -&amp;gt; Patreon -&amp;gt; Features #
The Plus additional features are:</description></item></channel></rss>